

ADIB RUZAINI BIN MOHD NAJIB

012-9184957

adib.ruzainimno@gmail.com

No. 12, Lorong Az-Zaharah 10/4A, Bandar Baru Puncak Alam, 42300 Puncak Alam, Selangor.

Date of Birth: **15th May 1991**Nationality: **Malaysian**Race: **Malay**Marital Status: **Single**

I am extremely determined to achieve goals. Highly motivated and love to learn new experiences. Meticulous and delivers high quality performance. A talent for observing and analysing problems given in any situation. Sincere and empathetic. Able to build a trust relationship and communicate well. Patient and flexible.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

Bachelor Degree in Mechanical Engineering (Hons). in UiTM, Shah Alam.

CGPA: 3.12

2009 - 2012

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering majoring in Aerospace in UiTM Permatang Pauh, Pulau Pinang.

CGPA: 2.69

EXPERIENCES

Shift Supervisor, Techno Mech (M) Sdn Bhd (May 2016 – Present)

- Directing, supervising or leading the erection personnel or group as a shift supervisor within my branch during overhaul work of Heavy Duty Gas Turbine Mechanical and Blading tasks.
- Coordinate erection supervision functions within the branch for technical correctness of erection activities in compliance with instructions.
- Ensure all tasks performed as according to Quality, Schedule, Environmental and Health & safety requirements.
- I am reporting to my superior according to project organization.

Date	Project/Machine Type	Job Function
16/5/2016 – 16/6/2016	Lumut GT21, Malaysia	
	C-Inspection, GT13E2M , Combine Cycle Gas	Night Shift Blader
	Turbine	
20/6/2016 – 30/6/2016	Prai GE, Malaysia	
	Generator shaft bearing replacement and Pre-	GT Mechanical
	alignment, Final-alignment, GE 9FA , Combine	
	Cycle Gas Turbine	
9/12/2016 – 24/12/2016	Port Dickson GE GT4, Malaysia	Day Shift Blader and GT Mechanical
	Hot gas path inspection, Turbine shaft bearing	
	and Generator shaft bearing inspection, Pre-	
	alignment and Final-alignment, GE 9, Combine	
	Cycle Gas Turbine	
28/12/2016 – 4/1/2017	Lumut GT21, Malaysia	
	C-Inspection, GT13E2M, Combine Cycle Gas	Day Shift Blader
	Turbine	

Intern, Subsea ROV (June 2014 - September 2014)

- Maintaining the equipment function to meet the requirement of International Maritime Contractor Association (IMCA) audit for the below equipment at the Kuantan Port:
 - Hydraulic Power Unit (HPU)
 - Mobile Workshop Container (33.2m³)
 - Control Van Container (33.2m³)
 - Launch and Recovery System
 - Remote Operated Vehicle (ROV)
- The maintenance scope for the equipment above includes:
 - Visual inspection of the unit/package to identify any obvious defect, to plan and execute the rectification work for any findings.
 - Replacement of the lube oil, hose and service the umbilical cord for the LARS unit connected to the ROV.
 - Troubleshooting the ROV camera, lighting and robotic arm.
 - Troubleshooting the LARS unit hydraulic system.
 - IMCA standard painting rectification job.
- Preparing project proposal for workshop consumable item by contacting the supplier and prepare the quotation.
- Preparing project proposal for ROV Workbench & Steel Structure Fabrication (Diver Platform) which
 contains:
 - Hands on in designing and fabricating of the bench and steel structure, forecast the man hours needed, preparing the tools and consumable items, preparing the project schedule and task to be perform, contacting the supplier for quotation, preparing the purchase order, controlling the budget and cost for the overall project.

Achievements:

- RC Plane Design (UiTM, Pulau Pinang)
 - Designing the plane wing aerofoil according to National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (NACA) standard.
- SAE Formula Car Design (UiTM, Shah Alam)
 - Designing a single seat car with complete feature for Society of Automotive Engineers (SAE)
 Formula Car. Include the fabrication and on track testing of the newly build car powered by 100 cc 4 stroke engine.
- Compression Chamber Fabrication (UiTM, Shah Alam)
 - Consist of air regulator and blow off valve that rated at 10 bar. The chamber is powered by air compression. The purpose of this chamber is to demonstrate the underwater pressure with increasing depth.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Language:

English, spoken and written: Fluent Malay, spoken and written: Fluent

Software and Hardware:

Software	Hardware
Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint,	Handling and using of various mechanical
Microsoft Excel	hand tools
Computer Aided Three Dimensional Interactive Application (CATIA)	Operating the lathe machine and CNC
Microsoft Visual Studio (Visual Basic, Visual C++)	Welding equipment (Arc weld, TIG)
	Precision measuring tools (Vernier calliper, micro meter, dial gauge etc)

CERTIFICATE

Date	Course	Institution
2016	Oil and Gas Safety Passport Level 1	NIOSH, Bangi
2015	Degree in Mechanical Engineering (Hons.) CGPA: 3.12	Universiti Teknologi Mara, Shah Alam
2011	Diploma in Mechanical Engineering CGPA : 2.69	UiTM Pulau Pinang, Permatang Pauh

^{*}Copy of the certificate will be available upon request.

REFERENCES

1) Ahmad Fahim bin Anuar

Sime Darby Industrial Sdn Bhd

No. 1, Jalan Puchong, Taman Perindustrian Puchong Utama,

47100 Puchong, Selangor Darul Ehsan, Malaysia.

Phn. No. +6012-4865722

Ext. No. +603-80688050

ahmad.fahim.anuar@simedarby.com

2) Syamsul Nizam bin Azmee

Bumi Subsea Malaysia Sdn Bhd – Gelang Patah Yard

No. 2, Jalan Mega 1/4, Taman Perindustrian Nusa Cemerlang,

79200 Nusajaya, Johor Bahru, Malaysia.

Phn. No. +6012-4883001

syamsul.azmi@bumi-subsea.com